Public Education Information Management System (PEIMS)

PEIMS is the statewide data collection system used by the Texas Education Agency (TEA) to collect information from Texas public school districts and charter schools.

The system collects:

• Student demographics
• Student academic performance
• Attendance records
• Personnel data
• Financial data
• Organizational data

PEIMS data is used for accountability ratings, state funding calculations, policy analysis, and statewide education reporting.

All Local Education Agencies (LEAs) are required to submit PEIMS data to TEA.
